PROPHECY TIME
Brother, where is your wife?
Because, it is terrible, the affection is dead.
Exactly.
As beautiful as she is - when you people are together in a closet,
it's like a man to man together.
Exactly, Man of God.
You'll just be looking at a beautiful person but you don't have affection again.
That is it, Man of God.
This is the problem in the house.
Exactly, Man of God.
STANDARD FOR LIFE
My name is Mr. Nnamdi Edozie. I'm from Anambra State.
The person here is my wife.
The prophecy the man of God gave to me was hundred percent true.
Last Sunday, the man of God came to me and asked me where my wife was.
And I said that this is my wife.
He said that there is no affection, that I don't have any affection for her.
He said that as beautiful as she is, there is no affection.
And I said, "Yes". Exactly - the prophecy is correct, hundred percent correct.
There was no affection between me and her.
In the house, she would fight me, do all sorts of things to me and beat me.
At times, I would sleep in the toilet until daybreak. Before I knew it, the day had broken.
At times, I would leave her when she was pursuing me and
I would go to another room.
If you would go where we are living, you'd see all the keys are broken.
She would break the key there, meet me and start fighting with me.
I don't want to touch her, I don't want to beat her, because I know she's...
So she used to beat you?
She used to beat me.
I even cook for her, wash her clothes, do all sorts of things because
when I entered my house, I would see everywhere was scattered.
I had to be doing things for myself. The two maids we had, she drove them away.
So it's only me and her that are living there.
I want to really thank you for your endurance.
And, assume you beat her back, a day like this would not come.
Assume you beat her back, you would not be talking today.
We would not talk of reconciliation today.
She beat you.
And each time she beats you, you run?
Yes, Man of God. I usually ran because I did not want to touch her.
I knew she was not herself.
She was just like a husband in the house.
I found out one thing,
Whenever I dreamt, I usually saw the spiritual husband in my dreams.
He always turned me to be a servant.
I would be cleaning the house, washing his vehicle
and he would be busy making love with my wife.
At the end of the day, after everything, I would be the one to ask my wife how everything was
and if she had enjoyed it.
And she would tell me that it was very okay. She enjoyed everything.
Even the man's manhood was very big.
Thank you. Today is the last day.
Uncle, this marriage is from God. And, the deliverance will take place.
You and your wife will be delivered.
You will now become a man, and your wife will become a woman.
You said you are the woman, and your wife is the man?
She is the husband at home
because I couldn't tell her anything that she would do. No no no, she can't do that.
The way she would do it - she takes my money and buy things.
Like today - she was asking me for money to do her hair, saying that
she would not come to the church without making her hair.
The last hair do she had was about 13,000 naira.
Ok, it's alright. It's alright
My brother, don't worry.
Don't worry. She will be a mother after the deliverance.
Don't worry. Everything will be over now.
She is a mother.
Yes.
This happened this morning. We were about to come to the church...
This morning?
Yes, Sir.
We were about to come to the church and
she said she could not come with her hair to the church. She couldn't do that.
What happened?
Accident?
She seized me.
She beat you?
She beat me and tore my dress.
This morning?
This morning.
Ok, it's alright, it's alright.
Don't show us the rest. Put it inside the bag.
It's alright.
I will not allow you to talk.
I will not allow you to talk. Don't worry.
I know the worst has happened. This woman - she will be your wife after the deliverance.
You will see her on her knees, giving you kiss. All what she has done to you...
You will enjoy this one. She is a good woman.
She is not the one doing all this.
The more you say it, the more ...hehehe. I don't want that hehehe.
No. Don't worry.
The rest...
I have many other things to say. There are so many.
Oh, my God!
As she is now, please, cameraman, focus on her face.
This face you see now, there is no kind of makeup...
Ok, camera, leave the face.
Ok, go and wait for me.
Come.
Is it a crime to put makeup?
Go and sit down. Put her near the air conditioning. Because makeup needs air conditioning.
Please, he should sit down. Come.
Come and sit here.
The makeup makes her look beautiful.
Ok, it's alright.
I want to tell you, this is a marriage from God.
I will prove it to you people with the power of God,
the power of the Holy Ghost.
STANDARD FOR LIFE
Following the instruction of the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua,
the husband and wife returned the next day for deliverance during the Monday Live Service.
Let's see what happened.
At the Synagogue Church of all Nations,
God Almighty moves mightily in the midst of the congregation,
using Wise Man Christopher as a medium to bring healing, deliverance and all of God's blessings.
Remember, satan comes to kill, steal and destroy.
But Jesus Christ came that we may have abundant life.
As Wise Man Christopher touches this lady,
the evil spirit inside of her immediately reacts to the spirit-filled touch
and begins to manifest.
Let's see how she was delivered, in the power of the Holy Ghost.
Speak out. Who are you?
Giant.
What have you done to her?
What do you mean by that?
I want to kill her.
What have you done to her husband and marriage?
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
This is trouble for me.
You are welcome, sir.
Who is this man to you?
I don't know.
You are welcome, sir.
She is my wife. We came together.
No, I don't know him.
What have you done to this marriage?
She is my wife.
Who is she to you?
For what?
I want to kill her.
Why do you want to kill her?
I want to kill her and kill that stupid man.
Why?
She is for me.
I love her so much.
You cannot do anything.
This man, if not for the love, they would have been dead by now.
I did it.
How? What happened?
What did you plan to do?
Accident. I want to kill them. It's too much, they are disturbing me.
I am a giant.
From where?
River.
These are my trucks that have had a series of accidents.
Even when we were coming, we had a terrible accident.
We were discharged from the hospital before we came here.
I was with her in my Jeep and just like that,
a car crashed into us head on.
We were unconscious.
My chest hit the steering wheel and I thought I was dead.
I knew there was danger. That's why I ran to The SCOAN to find a solution.
These are my trucks.
This one crashed into a commissioner's house, and I repaired the house.
This one killed 14 passengers.
This one crashed into the deputy commissioner's house and destroyed it.
I was the one that repaired it.
There were other ones. Another crashed into a river. It was a fuel tanker.
They took me to court and I had to pay approximately 2 million naira.
All the time, there would be accidents with both my personal and business vehicles.
All of them would have accidents.
What other evil things have you done?
Wait, let us have an agreement.
I don't talk much.
You are in the presence of God....
No, let us do it gently.
...where you cannot hide, speak!
I am mighty.
There is no child.
For what?
Who caused it?
I did.
Why?
She is my own.
For what? Why would I leave her?
Before she married this person, it was not easy.
I wanted to push her to somebody who would kill her - an occultic man
who would use her for rituals.
It was her mother.
That woman advised this person to take my wife.
How did you enter this body?
I entered her when she was in the market.
She used to be in her mother's shop, doing things and working well.
For what? Why should she be working well?
I don't want her to progress. I don't want her to shine.
That's why I entered her to destroy.
I will kill this man.
You cannot kill me.
Get away from me.
Right now, you are a stranger. Get out!
Come out of this body, you demon!
Move out!
All over your body, Holy Ghost fire!
All over your body, fire in the name of Jesus Christ!
Fire!
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Every part of your body!
Thank You, Lord, for her freedom.
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
In Jesus' Name.
Set Free in Jesus' Name
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Thank You, Jesus. Your are set free.
Set Free in Jesus' Name
How are you, ma?
How are you?
I am fine, sir.
Set Free in Jesus' Name
Come.
Can you see this man?
Baby, I am sorry.
I have forgiven you.
Set Free in Jesus' Name
Who is this man to you?
He is my husband.
He's who?
My husband.
You can see that the evil spirit being in her that spoke as the giant man,
has been cast out by Jesus.
Her past is over, and your past life of setback, accidents and the rest is also over.
Thank You, Jesus! We are free.
By the special grace of God, my mentor, Prophet T.B Joshua spoke to you yesterday
and, for one reason or the other, there was not enough time
because he was talking to a lot of people.
Now, you have been given the grace to explain what the demon in the life of your wife
was doing to you and your career.
My name is Mr Nnamdi Edozie. I'm from Anambra State.
I don't know how to start to thank God because what I have seen today
is what about 21 native doctors couldn't do.
It has happened here today.
Before we got married, we dated each other.
The very day we pronounced the date of our wedding is when everything started.
She was in the market one day and was rushed to the hospital because she was fainting.
I thought it was a very minor issue. I called my friend and we went to church.
When we got to the church, they said that her mother was the cause
but I said, "No, it cannot be her mother because her mother handed her over to me.
There is no way that it can be her mother".
That's how we started. We moved from one church to the other.
There is no church we have not attended.
I then thought that this could be something diabolical.
I then started going from one native doctor to the other.
Even when I went to native doctors,
I would ask them where I could find the highest native doctor
and they would take me to another native doctor.
That is how I started going everywhere.
You came yesterday and you were given a prophecy.
Do you remember what the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, told you?
Exactly.
How has your wife's character and attitude been like?
Her character caused that there was no peace in the house at all.
She didn't want to see me.
When I entered the house, she would do all sorts of things, beat me.
She can't cook.
For her hair, she would tell me that she wanted to buy a N60,000 wig.
I would say, "No, how can you buy a N60,000 wig?"
She would want to spend money recklessly but I would say, "No".
Whenever she needed that kind of money and I refused, it caused a fight;
she would fight me.
If you went into the house, everything would be untidy.
She couldn't even wash her clothes. I was the one doing the housework.
I would wash my clothes and hers and even wash her underwear.
There are so many things...
If she managed to cook,
either the salt would be too much or the pepper would be too much.
So I told her, "Stop cooking, I will do it myself".
It was going like that.
Everything started turning upside down.
I'm into transport business.
My vehicles started having problems, getting into one accident and another.
The business was not moving normally.
I knew there was something behind it.
Usually in my dreams, I would see this man.
Even sometimes, I would tell him to come out and let us fight.
He was a very tall, giant man.
When we slept, early in the morning, if I looked at her eyes,
a kind of sparkle would sparkle in my eyes.
I used to see her spiritual husband in a very big house with a vehicle.
He turned me into a servant there.
I used to wash the vehicle and sweep the house.
The spiritual husband would come and take my wife with pride,
enter the house and make love with my wife.
Afterwards, he wouldhug her, laugh and come out.
Then, I would ask my wife what happened.
My wife said that the whole thing was sweet, that it was not small
and that she enjoyed everything.
I was helpless; there was nothing I could do.
I would have the same dreams.
The spiritual husband would come to me also in my dreams.
He told me, "Look, my friend, forget about your manhood;
I have taken it".
At daybreak, I thought it was an ordinary dream.
I found out that my manhood was not working very well.
That was how life was going.
At times, she would say that she wanted to die.
She would take a knife and try to stab herself.
I would be the one that would stop her.
I couldn't go anywhere because I believed that one day she would kill herself.
Even when she was sleeping, I would watch her and every ten minutes, I would wake her.
After she opened her eyes, I would tell her to continue sleeping.
That was how I had been keeping vigil over her.
That's how the whole thing started.
You can't tell her something and see that she does it. No!
She would like to command you. She would like to tell you what to do.
At times I used to ask her, "Are you the one who married me or am I the one that married you?
She would say that she was the one that owned the house.
Glory be to God, you came yesterday
and Prophet T.B. Joshua, my mentor, spoke to you
and told you exactly what you have explained to us now.
The grace of God in his life has put an end to this trouble.
Thank You, Jesus!
Thank You, Jesus! We are delivered!
TESTIMONY TIME
Nothing and no one on this earth except God could have reconciled this marriage
because the reconciliation demanded deliverance.
The man is the one kissing, not the woman.
The man is the one kneeling down, not the woman.
So, all that we were saying while she was standing,
she was just looking at me - "What is happening here."
That day, I said to the whole world, after the deliverance,
the woman would be the one to be on her knees, taking the responsibility of a woman,
and the man would also take the responsibility of a man
and the whole thing would be reconciled. I said it to the whole world.
So, now I know the whole world is waiting.
What happened now? That is what we want to hear.
Secondly, the lesson you have to learn here is that God will not prepare a free woman,
a woman that is so free from everything for you to marry,
or a man that is free for you to marry.
You have to do some adjustments, jobs.
It is like when you buy a car.
You can't just take a car and say this is a new car and begin to use it.
You still have some jobs to do.
In the life of man, in the life of woman.
If you know this medically, so you should know this spiritually.
Medically, when you meet a woman you want to marry, or a woman wants to marry a man,
the first thing you'll want to know is the medical state of the man
and the medical state of the woman.
No matter whether the woman says that she is a pastor or born-again or whatever,
you need to know the spiritual state of the woman, and
the woman needs to know the spiritual state of the man.
But we have failed to do that.
We only face one side of life.
We are interested in the medical state of a man before marrying him
and the medical state of the woman before marrying her.
That is the only thing that appeals to us in all marriages in the world.
That is why there is trouble in marriages today.
If I'm talking to you, let me see your hand.
Emmanuel! (God with us - Matthew 1:23)
If God is with us, nobody can be against us at all.
My name is Mr Nnamdi Dozie.
The person beside me here is my lovely wife.
I dont know how to say this, how to qualify this.
I'm short of words for what God has done in my life.
Let me start from Prophet T.B. Joshua.
People call him pastor T.B. Joshua,
other people call him Prophet T.B. Joshua.
That man that you are seeing there is more than a prophet.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
He is God sent.
God sent him to set the world free,
to deliver the world and set people out of their bondages.
He did it in my life.
I have testified, I have seen and I have conquered.
I have my reason for saying this.
My reason is that, something that almost 50 churches could not do,
almost 21 herbalists could not do, he did it.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I have gone to many churches, there was nowhere I had not gone to.
Even at times they would ask me to sow a seed that would provoke God.
They said that when God was provoked, my problem would be over.
However, the more I sowed the seed, the more my problem got tougher.
I then decided that this was not a church issue. Maybe it was a diabolical thing.
That is how I started going to herbalists.
There was no herbalist in the east that I had not gone to looking for a solution.
There was no place I had not gone to searching for a solution.
It got to the extent that wherever I went, I would be asking people,
where I could get the highest herbalist that would solve my problem
and they always took me to them.
There was even one herbalist that was called a name which meant
somebody who could solve all problems.
I went there.
The herbalist called his oracle, called my name. I didn't tell him my name.
He called my name and said, "Welcome".
He told me all my problems.
He told me there was a solution.
He charged me a lot of money and I paid.
Yet, everything remained the same. There was no solution.
It happened that this oracle started telling me many things
like there was a woman I befriended who was behind everything.
I believed because the oracle could call my name and tell me what brought me.
I had every confidence in this oracle and I started chasing shadows.
Everything this oracle said, I did it - bring such and such amount of money.
To the extent that I deposited my vehicle in an attempt to pay the balance.
Still, the problem remained the same.
It is by the grace of God that I got the cable and searched for Emmanuel TV.
That is how I saw what is happening here.
When I saw what was happening here, I started to imagine that I should come.
When I was coming here, I was coming to test.
I was coming to test whether it would work out.
There is no place I had not gone to.
There was something that happened that I want to narrate.
During the prophecy, we were sitting on our seats.
The man of God came and prophesied to somebody who was behind my wife
and then prophesied to somebody who was behind me.
He even prophesied to somebody in front of me.
He also prophesied to somebody behind me.
When you are prophesied to, the ushers always take you out.
It happened that I was the only one left on the seat with my wife.
I told her in slang that it seemed the spiritual husband had covered the man of God's face.
Praise the Lord!
Please, take it back again because I could not hear very well.
You said, when I entered and began to prophesy - start from there.
When you prophesied to somebody in front of me, behind me and beside my wife.
It was only my wife left.
I believed that my problem was more than of those you prophesied to.
That was when I told my wife that it seemed
the spiritual husband had covered man of God's eyes so that he could not see us.
My wife said, "Yes, it seems so. Don't worry.
When we leave, we will go to that witchdoctor we haven't been to yet".
Inside the church?
Yes, that was what we were saying in our minds.
While we were discussing this, it was as if the man of God heard
what we were discussing and turned back.
When he turned back, he passed my seat again, reversed and passed me again.
You know when you are expecting something from someone,
you would watch his every movement.
Then, as he passed, it was as if there was an electric shock that hit him
and he stopped, turned to me and said, "Brother, can I talk to you?"
I said to myself that this man must be a powerful man.
That was when he gave me the prophecy
and went directly to tell me what was happening in my life.
My people have a parable that says: Anything you wear on your hand
you do not need a mirror to look at it.
As you can see, my wife is a wife to me now.
This was a woman that did not want to see me.
This was a woman who, after cooking, she would walk to the dustbin and pour it away.
Since when? For how many years?
About two and a half years.
You people have been living in this trouble?
Exactly, Man of God.
This was a woman that would never be happy.
When she looked in the mirror, she would tell me that she saw another person.
This was a woman that would tell me something was telling her
to remove all her clothers and begin to run naked.
This was a woman that wherever she was, she was not happy.
She would bring out a knife and want to kill herself.
I would be the one to take the knife from her. I would be the one guiding her.
A lot happened in our lives.
The only thing that has happened now is that she has changed my name to "Baby Boy".
Before then, she didn't use to call my name: "Who is this? I beg, get out."
That was how she had been behaving at home.
But now she always calls out, "Baby boy, where are you?"
Madam, since that Sunday, what has happened in your vision, your dreams, when you sleep?
Tell us - what happened, and the man too - what happened?
After my deliverance, I dreamt and saw the spiritual husband coming to take me
and use me to make pepper soup.
Then, they said they have caught him.
They cut him into pieces and used him to make pepper soup. So, he died.
In the past, he used to appear to you, sometimes physically when you were alone?
Yes, before my deliverance, I used to see him.
When I was alone, it would be as if someone was telling me something.
If I looked behind me, I would not see anybody.
It would be as if somebody passed me. I would not see anybody.
I would always be afraid. I couldn't sleep alone.
Even in the house, it couldn't be alone there.
Before my deliverance, I could never be happy - no matter what I had.
It didn't matter what I ate or where I was taken; it only added to the anger.
If I was dressing up, I would look in the mirror and I would not be seeing myself.
It would be as if I was looking at a hundred year old person.
I would ask my husband if he saw me or saw what I was seeing too.
He would say it was me, but I would say that I did not see myself.
The more I said this, the more angry I became.
There was no affection at all. There was nothing he did that made me happy.
Even if he did something that would make me happy, that is when I would be more angry.
But now, I am the happiest woman on earth.
Wow, did you listen to that? There is affection now?
Yes, Man of God. I love my husband so much now.
I learnt you are calling him "baby".
Yes, he's my "Baby Boy".
You have listened to that?
Thank you.
Oh, this is a lesson to everyone,
to everyone of us.
Because of all this, there is marry and re-marry.
Assume they were able to have a child, they would have a child that is possessed.
It's better that they have no child.
Now, they're delivered they can have a child.
I did not mention the aspect of affection.
The affection now is wonderful, just like an electric shock.
We don't want that electric shock to shock you inside the church. So, glory be to God!
You have spent so much.
Can you quantify how much you have spent in the process of delivering this lady?
Man of God, I can't estimate this.
But in terms of physical cash, I think I have spent more than 15 million naira.
I am not talking in terms of my trucks and other vehicles that had accidents and spoilt.
How many vehicles had accidents?
It was three trucks plus my personal jeep, making four all together.
Which involved 15 people?
Yes, Man of God.
Died.
My advice to couples all over the world especially people that are passing through so many things,
they are supposed to learn from my experience
that there is nothing God cannot do.
70 percent of homes today are broken because of this spiritual attack.
When you, because of evil spirit, divorce a woman and end the marriage,
satan will arrange the most beautiful woman with your desired appearance somewhere -
waiting for you.
The next woman you marry will have a greater evil spirit than the one you left.
You cannot escape it. If you because of evil spirit ... we don't divorce because of evil spirit.
If you do that, it's dangerous.
Very dangerous. Are you talking of suicide?
This is the spirit that makes people commit suicide.
People like her.
If this deliverance had not happened at this time,
she would have hung herself or made use of a drug - sleep and not wake up.
Hang or stab herself.
Or jump inside the sea.
Or run onto the express road.
That is the spirit of suicide. It would tell you, "Go and do this" and that is it.
The same spirit in her can affect the husband to do the same, to commit suicide
because frustration would lead the husband to do that.
So, can you imagine the suicide that is going on all over the world today? All over.
You can't because of frustration, commit suicide - but the spirit of frustration.
You can't because of poverty, commit suicide - the spirit of poverty.
You can't because of sickness die - the spirit of sickness.
Are you with me? If I'm talking to you, let me see your hand.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances, sermons and testimonies,
from the Synagogue Church of all Nations.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations and Changing the world.